desi-radio.com 2016-03-29

# DeSi-RaDiO.com - Best Indian & Pakistani Music Online, Listen Rare, Old and New Hindi & Urdu Songs in High Quality

**Privacy Policy**

DeSi-RaDiO.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: DeSi-RaDiO.com 

**Information Automatically Logged**

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is also used for keeping track of voting, and for song requests.

**Advertisers**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. 
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. 
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

**Registration Forms**

Our site's (forum and possibly others) registration form requires users to give us contact information , unique identifiers , and demographic information. Contact information from the registration forms is used to get in touch with the customer when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Unique identifiers are collected from Web site visitors to verify the user's identity, and for use as account numbers in our record system. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences.

**External Links**

This site contains links to other sites. DeSi-RaDiO.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

**Public Forums**

This site makes forums available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

**Choice/Opt-Out**

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving promotional/marketing information from us . You can follow the simple instructions in the mail you recieved.

**Contacting the Web Site**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact the administrator
